Prasad Madusanka

Full Stack Developer

About Me

Hello, I'm a Full Stack Developer with more than 1 year industrial experience and around 1 year experience in freelance development.

And I'm an undergraduate joiner with strong and well developed industrial skills and experience in Web development. Also i have freelance experience in Mobile apps & Standalone application development including design, delivering and maintenance.



Career Experience

2018 - Present Freelance

Currently I'm working as a freelance developer on several projects from October 2018. I use Angular, Spring Boot, Node JS & MongoDB as technologies.

2017 - 2018 Virtusa Pvt Ltd

From June 2017 to October 2018 I worked as Junior Software Engineer at **Virtusa Pvt Ltd** CMB and i involved in an On-site project as a Software Engineer and also worked on Internal projects. I have used Angular, Java, Javacript, Node JS, Shell & Batch Scripts, Spring Boot, MongoDB, OrientDB and many technologies.

2016 - 2017 Freelance

Worked as a freelance developer on several projects from 2016 to June 2017. I use Android, HTML, CSS, Javascript as technologies

Academic Qualifications

| 2017 - Present | BSc (Hons.) in Computer Science National School of Business Management Expecting to complete the degree offered by University College Dublin - Ireland |
|----------------|--|
| 2016 - 2017 | Higher Diploma in Computer Based Information Systems National Institute of Business Management Successfully completed the second year with GPA of 3.61 |
| 2016 - 2015 | Diploma in Computer System Design National Institute of Business Management Successfully completed the first year with GPA of 3.71 |
| 2012 - 2013 | Oracle Certified Professional Java Programmer Java Institute for Advance Technology Sri Lanka Completed the course |
| 2012 - 2013 | Java Standalone Application Development (JSAD) Java Institute for Advance Technology Sri Lanka |

Projects

I have developed and deployed several Android apps, Websites and Standalone solutions. Complete description available on 'https://www.prasadmadusanka.me'

Completed the course

Contacts

- (+94) 777 578 947
- prasad.mads@gmail.com
- www.prasadmadusanka.me
- in/prasad-madusanka

Skills

- · Web, Mobile development
- Microservice development

Languages & Frameworks

- Angular 4, 5 & 6
- React, Vue JS
- Javascript, Typescript
- Node JS, Express JS
- Java, Spring Boot
- Android, NativeScript
- Shell & Batch Scripts
- •HTML, SCSS & CSS
- C#

Databases & Servers

- MongoDB, OrientDB
- MS SQL
- Tomcat, PM2, Nginx

Cloud Services

AWS, Google Cloud Services

Tools

- VSCode
- JetBrains IDE's
- Eclipse, Netbeans
- Postman, SOAP UI

Operating Systems

- MacOS
- Linux
- Windows